Guide to the Lorin Edgar Kerr Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Writings, 1943-1978; Series III; 1 linear feet (3 boxes)
  - "The Prevention of Occupational Illness and Injury: A Reality," American Public Health Association, Los Angeles: speech text, 1978 October 18 (Box 49, Folder 72)
  - "Black Lung: A Case Study": text, undated (Box 49, Folder 73)
  - Coal Workers' Pneumoconiosis in the United States, with others, Academy Press: chapter drafts, undated (Box 49, Folder 74)
  - Coal Workers' Pneumoconiosis in the United States, with others, Academy Press: chapter draft, undated (Box 49, Folder 75)
- Personal Papers, 1962-1978; Series IV; 0.25; (1 box)
  PERSONAL PAPERS is arranged chronologically.
  - Correspondence, 1962-1973 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Biographical sketch and personnel form, 1965, 1971, 1976, 1981, undated (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Newsclippings re: activities, 1967-1968 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Newsclippings re: appointments, 1969-1972 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Newsclippings re: activities, 1969-1972, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1974-1978, undated (Box 50, Folder 6-8)
  - Photographs (Goldie Krantz), undated (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Additional Material, Accession 1998-M-128
  - Journal [as county health officer, Iron County, Michigan], 1941 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Letter from Tony Boyle, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)